

#### **DATOS DE CONTACTO**

Celular: (+54) 9 2477 595326

Correo: francoaugustoacosta@gmail.com

Portfolio: ffran-acosta.netlify.app

LinkedIn: @ffran-acosta GitHub: ffran-acosta

Localidad: Pergamino, Buenos Aires,

Argentina

## **PERFIL PERSONAL**

Me llamo Franco, tengo 27 años y me gradué recientemente como Desarrollador Web en Digital House. Soy una persona proactiva con ganas de seguir aprendiendo nuevas tecnologías y me siento a gusto trabajando tanto en el frontend, como en el backend.

#### **SKILLS**

- JavaSctipt
  Python Patrón de
- React Java
  - **MVC**

arquitectura

- NodeJS • SOL
- Express • GIT Postman
- TypeScript Sequelize Creacion y
- HTML Metodolgías consumo de
- CSS ágiles -**APIs**
- EJS Scrum

#### **FORTALEZAS**

- Personalidad Proactiva
- · Resolución de problemas
- Adaptación a equipos de trabajo existentes
- · Capacidad de liderazgo
- · Excelentes relaciones interpersonales
- Alta captación de aprendizaje
- · Dedicación y compromiso
- Autocritico
- · Carnet de conducir (nacional)

# FRANCO ACOSTA

# FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

### **EXPERIENCIA PROFESIONAL**

# OXIGENO: e-commerce (06/2022 - 12/2022)

Como parte del equipo de desarrollo, me desempeñé como desarrollador full stack en OXIGENO, un e-commerce asignado como proyecto integrador en la edtech Digital House. Con la técnica de desarrollo scrum el proyecto fue realizado en NodeJs utilizando tecnologías como HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Express, MySql, Sequelize, Git entre otras.

# **Editor (2022)**

Me desempeño actualmente editando fotos y videos con el pack Creative Cloud de Adobe para la productora Muzzo Visions, Miami, Florida, USA.

Contacto: Nicolás Muzzioli (+1) 214 4860673

# Venta de Hardware y reparación de pc (2020 - 2022)

Elaboración de presupuesto, armados, reparación y reacondicionamiento de PC y notebook. (Emprendimiento)

## **RUTH SAGER (11/2017 - 9-2020)**

Industria alimenticia. Durante el primer año desempeñándome en la elaboración, envasado y preparación para distribución del producto. Durante el segundo periodo en área administrativa.

Contacto: Eugenio Berasain (02474-15404883)

## FORMACION ACADEMICA

#### **DIGITAL HOUSE**

- Programación Web Full Stack, 2022

## **UNNOBA Pergamino**

- Lic. en Sistemas 2018/21

#### **UTN Rosario**

- Ingeniería en Sistemas 2017

#### **IDIOMAS**

**ESPAÑOL - Nativo** 

INGLES - Avanzado 8 años Instituto KEN



#### **DATOS DE CONTACTO**

Phone: (+54) 9 2477 595326

Correo: francoaugustoacosta@gmail.com

Portfolio: ffran-acosta.netlify.app

LinkedIn: @ffran-acosta GitHub: ffran-acosta

Location: Pergamino, Buenos Aires,

Argentina

## **PERFIL PERSONAL**

My name is Franco, I am 27 years old and I recently graduated as a Full Stack Web Developer at Digital House. I am a proactive person with a desire to continue learning new technologies and I feel comfortable working both on the frontend and backend.

## **SKILLS**

- JavaSctipt
  Python
- React Java
- NodeJS SOL
- Express GIT

HTML

EJS

- TypeScript Sequelize Scrum
- Postman Creation and

MVC

(Model-

view-

- CSS

methodology consumption

controller)

of APIs

#### **STRENGTHS**

- Proactive personality
- · Problem-solving skills
- · Adaptability to existing work teams
- Leadership ability
- · Excellent interpersonal relationships
- High learning ability
- · Dedication and commitment
- · Self-critical
- · National driver's license

# FRANCO ACOSTA

# FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

## **EXPERIENCE**

# OXIGENO: e-commerce (06/2022 - 12/2022)

As part of the development team, I worked as a full-stack web developer at OXIGENO, an e-commerce assigned as an integrative project in the edtech Digital House. Using the scrum development technique, the project was completed using NodeJs technologies such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Express, MySql, Sequelize, Git, among others.

# **Editor (2022)**

I am currently working on editing photos and videos using the Adobe Creative Cloud pack for the production company Muzzo Visions, Miami, Florida, USA.

Reference: Nicolás Muzzioli (+1) 214 4860673

# Venta de Hardware y reparación de pc (2020 - 2022)

Budget preparation, assembly, repair, and refurbishment of PC and laptops. (Entrepreneurship)

# **RUTH SAGER (11/2017 - 9-2020)**

Food industry. During the first year, I worked in the production, packaging, and preparation for distribution of the product. During the second period in the administrative area, I developed a system for stock control, quality control, and distribution.

Reference: Eugenio Berasain (02474-15404883)

## FORMACION ACADEMICA

#### **DIGITAL HOUSE**

- Full Stack Web Developer, 2022

## **UNNOBA Pergamino**

- Bachelor of Systems 2018/21

#### **UTN Rosario**

- Systems Engineering 2017

#### **IDIOMAS**

**SPANISH - Native** 

**INGLES - Avanzado** 

8 years at KEN Institute